destinationlighting.com 2018-07-02

# Frequently Asked Questions | Destination Lighting

* * *

Why do you need my e-mail address?

When you make a purchase, your e-mail address is used to send automated confirmation messages. The e-mail will contain important information about the transaction for shipping and tracking purposes.

Will my e-mail address be used for purposes other than purchasing, shipping and tracking information?

While we do not disclose or sell personal information such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address or telephone number to third party companies, we retain the right to use your information for our own marketing purposes. All registered users will receive the our newsletter and may receive other promotional offers from Destination Lighting. Users can choose to opt-in (subscribe) or opt-out (unsubscribe) at any time. Please read our Privacy Policy for more details.

Is the information I give you secure?

All orders are encrypted with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which encrypts all of your personal information so that it cannot be read as it travels over the Internet. If you wish to order by telephone, please contact the Support department.

What Web browsers can I use?

Destination Lighting supports the latest version of Internet Explorer 8+, Firefox, Safari and Chrome and Opera.

Do you use cookies?

Destination Lighting uses cookies on our Web site. A cookie is a small alphanumeric identifier that our Web server places on your browser to uniquely identify you as a visitor to our Web site. Cookies enable Destination Lighting to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Destination Lighting cookies do not collect personally identifiable information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are. Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies. However, cookies need to be enabled to effectively shop the Destination Lighting Web site.

Will you sell or rent my e-mail address to other companies?

We do not sell, rent or give away any identifiable personal information to any third party. Read our complete Privacy Policy for more information.

What happens if I don't complete my transaction?

If you do not complete the full transaction, the order will not be submitted for processing.

Why am I having problems displaying this site?

Destination Lighting supports the latest version of Internet Explorer, Firefox, Chrome, Safari and Opera. If you are experiencing difficulties, it is likely because you are using an outdated version of your browser or you need to make sure you have javascript enabled on your browser.

What do you do with my credit card information?

We have taken many steps to ensure the security of your personal information. We never keep your credit card information in our Internet database. We protect sensitive information you give us by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information you submit. This allows us to validate your data and provides us with a method to receive payment from you.

What is your privacy policy?

#### Privacy Policy

At Destination Lighting, we are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. Because we take your right to privacy seriously, we developed this privacy statement to inform you about our privacy practices. Destination Lighting respects each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at Destination Lighting's Web site. By visiting Destination Lighting's Web site, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. If our policy on information collection or uses changes, we will update the information accordingly on this page.

#### Personal Information You Provide to Us

Destination Lighting collects personal information you provide to us when shopping our Web site such as your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. We may also collect information which our users divulge about others when making a referral, sharing a Wish List or sending a Web page URL to a friend. You may choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may limit your ability to use our Web site. The personal information you provide is used for such purposes as delivering products or services to you, responding to your requests for certain information, customizing content you see and communicating with you about new products and special promotions. Destination Lighting will not disclose or sell personal information such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address or telephone number. By shopping with us, you agree that we may use your information for our own marketing purposes.

#### Personal information Collected Automatically

We collect the following general data that is not personally identifiable information when you interact with our Web site or services: your IP address, time and date of your visit, cookie information and the page(s) you requested. We automatically receive and record such general information on our server logs from your browser. We collect demographic data in order to provide a better shopping experience for our customers and the information is collected involuntarily. We collect this information through methods such as registration forms, clickstream tracking and log files. To receive our products and services, some information we collect is mandatory because this is how we ship products to you and track your order. Other information we request is optional.

#### E-mail Communication

Destination Lighting offers registered users the option to receive regular communication about our products and services via email. By default, all registered users will automatically receive our newsletter and promotional codes. You can opt-out of this email subscription at any time by deselecting the check box on the My Account page, then saving your user settings. You can also discontinue your subscription by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link found in the body of your emailed newsletter message. If you would like to subscribe to our newsletter, simply leave the check box selected during registration or return to the My Account page. You may also opt-in by supplying your first and last name and email address on our list management site.

There are certain e-mails that Destination Lighting may continue to send per your request or that are necessary for you to receive the full benefit of our services. For example, we use e-mail to deliver information that registered users request, as well as provide details about customer account(s), delivery information, and operational information regarding existing products, services and systems.

#### Cookies

Destination Lighting uses cookies on our Web site. A cookie is a small alphanumeric identifier that our Web server places on your browser to uniquely identify you as a visitor to our Web site. Cookies enable Destination Lighting to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Destination Lighting cookies do not collect personally identifiable information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are. Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies. However, cookies need to be enabled to effectively shop the Destination Lighting Web site.

#### Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.  
You can find details outlined here: <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

##### We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

##### We have implemented the following:

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

##### Opting out:

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on. 

Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on can be found here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

#### Information Usage

We will supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources such as credit history reports to authorize purchases. We may share data with third parties including shipping companies (United Parcel Service) and credit card companies used for the transaction (Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover). These third parties will use the data for shipping and billing purposes only, and users cannot opt out of sharing their information with the above third parties.

We rely on other companies and individuals to perform tasks on our behalf and we share your information with them so we can provide products and services to you. Some of these tasks include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. Unless we communicate otherwise, agents of Destination Lighting do not use personal information we share with them beyond what is necessary for us to serve you.

#### Data Storage and Security

Destination Lighting takes considerable precautions to protect your personal information from loss, misuse and alteration with our state-of-the-art servers. No credit card information is stored on our Internet database. We believe your personal information should be protected.

We use the latest encryption technology to keep your personal information safe. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to ensure the security of your personal and order information. All your ordering information-including your name, address, and credit card number-is encrypted over a secure channel for maximum security.

Why do you need my telephone number?

When you make a purchase, we require a telephone number to complete your shipping transaction. It also gives us a way of contacting you should we need to.
